{
    "kind": "Unscramble",
    "questions": [
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP2M1L2c.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the letters. What's the vegetable?",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "gacabeb",
                    "answer": "cabbage"
                },
                {
                    "question": "colcirob",
                    "answer": "broccoli"
                },
                {
                    "question": "nonio",
                    "answer": "onion"
                },
                {
                    "question": "reeng nabes",
                    "answer": "green beans"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ottapose",
                    "answer": "potatoes"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ceettlu",
                    "answer": "lettuce"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP2M1L3c.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the words using a code. Code: use the alphabet backwards (Z=A, A=Z)",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "YOVMWVI",
                    "answer": "blender"
                },
                {
                    "question": "KVKKVI",
                    "answer": "pepper"
                },
                {
                    "question": "HGLEV",
                    "answer": "stove"
                },
                {
                    "question": "KLG",
                    "answer": "pot"
                },
                {
                    "question": "HZOG",
                    "answer": "salt"
                },
                {
                    "question": "XSVU",
                    "answer": "chef"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP2M1L5b.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the sentences",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "good you for are Carrots",
                    "answer": "Carrots are good for you."
                },
                {
                    "question": "donuts I like.",
                    "answer": "I like donuts"
                },
                {
                    "question": "bad for your Sugar is teeth",
                    "answer": "Sugar is bad for your teeth."
                },
                {
                    "question": "vegetables Eat every day and fruit",
                    "answer": "Eat fruits and vegetables every day."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP2M2L7a.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the sentences.",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "like / We / sneakers. / these",
                    "answer": "We like these sneakers."
                },
                {
                    "question": "pants. / I / need / don't / new",
                    "answer": "I don't need new pants."
                },
                {
                    "question": "bow / tie / you / Do / want / a / ?",
                    "answer": "Do you want a bow tie? "
                },
                {
                    "question": "like / you / shirt / this / Do / ?",
                    "answer": "Do you like this shirt?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "find / I / can't / my / barrettes / new / ! ",
                    "answer": "I can't find my new barrettes!"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP2M3L13a.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the instructions.",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "life jacket / your / leave / Don't / on the ground.",
                    "answer": "Don't leave your life jacket on the ground."
                },
                {
                    "question": "tent / your / in / Put it. ",
                    "answer": "Put it in your tent."
                },
                {
                    "question": "trash / in the ocean / throw / Don't ",
                    "answer": "Don't throw trash in the ocean."
                },
                {
                    "question": "in / Put it / the trash can.",
                    "answer": "Put it in the trash can."
                },
                {
                    "question": "by the fire / Don't / the food / leave. ",
                    "answer": "Don't leave food by the fire."
                },
                {
                    "question": "the sausages / Put / the food box / in",
                    "answer": "Put the sausages in the food box."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP2M3L13b.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the verbs",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "hwort",
                    "answer": "throw"
                },
                {
                    "question": "veela",
                    "answer": "leave"
                },
                {
                    "question": "upt",
                    "answer": "put"
                },
                {
                    "question": "eancl",
                    "answer": "clean"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP2M4L19a.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the questions",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "people / How many / in your family / there / are /?",
                    "answer": "How many people are there in your family?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "are / How many / there / children / in the class? ",
                    "answer": "How many children are there in the class?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "boys / many / there / How / are?",
                    "answer": "How many boys are there? "
                },
                {
                    "question": "many / girls / are / How / there / ? ",
                    "answer": "How many girls are there?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "there / many / How / in the bookcase / books / ? / are",
                    "answer": "How many books are there in the bookcase? "
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}